Summary

Tech project manager seeks new role in management or communications. Open to a wide range of positions, including (but not limited to) product management, business/data analysis, executive assisting, and event programming. Previous experience in project management, tech development, and seed-stage ventures.

Work Experience

Tech Consultant - Capgemini US, New York NY

Scrum Master (Project Manager)

Jun. 2022 – Present Aug. 2022 - Mar. 2023

- Certifications: PMS1 Scrum Master, AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals
- Facilitated Scrum (project management) practices for client's machine learning team, including scheduling, goal setting, collaboration, and documentation.
- Developed Microsoft Azure DevOps Dashboards, Queries, Roadmaps, etc. to optimize team efficiency.
- Calculated and analyzed sprint metrics such as velocity and accuracy.

Data Analyst Intern – NYU Leslie Entrepreneurial Institute, New York NY

Community Programs Intern

Apr. 2021 – May 2022

Sep. 2021 - Apr. 2021 Sep. 2019 – May 2020

Analyzed aggregate data from Institute events by creating a behavioral network.

- Used software tools like PyVis and Pandas to plot user behavior throughout programs.
- Developed software to clean, organize, and analyze data.
- Completed several interim assignments and a final project report directly to the entire Institute staff.

Education

Office Intern

New York University, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences

Sep. 2018 – May 2022

GPA: 3.6

Major in Computer Science Minors in Mathematics and Italian

Academic Memberships: Tech@NYU, NYU Entrepreneurs Network, Bite Club at NYU

Societies: LGBTQ+ in Tech, Botmakers

Coding Languages: Python, Java, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, C/C++

Projects

Network Analysis (GitHub Link)

- Created a behavioral network from event data for NYU's Entrepreneurial Institute.
- Developed adjacency data and network visualization to demonstrate trends in the data.

Movie Review Sentiment Analysis (*GitHub Link*)

- Calculated binary classification and logistic regression to determine sentiment for 50,000 IMDb movie reviews.
- Used machine learning tools such as SciKit Learn, Jupyter Notebook, and NLTK to parse reviews and perform analysis.

Daily Tarot Bot

- Created a Twitter bot that tweets a tarot card once a day with meaningful advice.
- Learned Python's Tweepy library, GitHub Actions flows, project scheduling, API handling, and version control.